// Question Types
// 1. MCQs | Multiple Choice | single
// 2. boolean | true/false | single
// 3. MAQs | Multiple Answers | multiple

import { Topic } from '.'

export const Q014: Topic = {
  topic: 'TOEIC Part 5',
  level: 'Beginner',
  totalQuestions: 10,
  totalScore: 10,
  totalTime: 100,
  questions: [
    {
      question: 'Reza West Consulting has been actively recruiting employees with ------ backgrounds.',
      choices: ['diversely', 'diversify', 'diversity', 'diverse'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['diverse'],
      score: 1,
    },
    {
      question: 'Please be very careful when disclosing our ------ information to outside parties.',
      choices: ['moderate', 'confidential', 'prosperous', 'confident'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['confidential'],
      score: 1,
    },
    {
      question: 'For a ------ time only, Abilos Fitness Gym is offering a free one------month trial for new members.',
      choices: ['limitedly', 'limited', 'limitation', 'limiting'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['limited'],
      score: 1,
    },
    {
      question: 'Monday is the most convenient day for ------ to hold our department meetings.',
      choices: ['our', 'us', 'ours', 'we'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['us'],
      score: 1,
    },
    {
      question: 'Please be sure to follow the attached ------ when assembling our furniture.',
      choices: ['instructions', 'destinations', 'connections', 'appointments'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['instructions'],
      score: 1,
    },
    {
      question: 'At Rosen Technologies, rigorous testing was repeatedly conducted to improve the ------ of the products.',
      choices: ['reliable', 'relies', 'reliably', 'reliability'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['reliability'],
      score: 1,
    },
    {
      question: 'The North Hilltop Hotel where we are staying this weekend is located on a hill ------ the lake.',
      choices: ['overseeing', 'overlooking', 'transferring', 'undergoing'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['overlooking'],
      score: 1,
    },
    {
      question: 'Many real estate companies are ------ using Internet advertisements to obtain rental contracts for apartments.',
      choices: ['acting', 'active', 'actively', 'action'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['actively'],
      score: 1,
    },
    {
      question: 'If a new bridge ------ in the northwest part of the city, it would have reduced traffic congestion during the commute.',
      choices: ['was built', 'built', 'had been building', 'had been built'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['had been built'],
      score: 1,
    },
    {
      question: 'In recent years, interest in ------ energy sources such as solar and wind power has increased.',
      choices: ['renew', 'renewable', 'renewal', 'renewably'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['renewable'],
      score: 1,
    },
  ],
}